{
    "id": "869e51dfc7ca4114807db336057a1eb9",
    "title": "Articles Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "I was born in …………………",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "May",
                "the May",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "My brother lives in …………………",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Mumbai",
                "the Mumbai",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "We watched …………….. yesterday.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "movie",
                "a movie",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Festivals are …………………. to celebrate.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "occasion",
                "an occasion",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "When ……………… sets, darkness descends.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "sun",
                "the sun",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "The birds were pecking at ………………",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "tree",
                "the tree",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I will never forget your acts of ………………..",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "kindness",
                "the kindness",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Milk is the best food for ………………..",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "baby",
                "a baby",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "………………. arrived on time.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Train",
                "The train",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Give me ……………….",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "pen",
                "a pen",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        }
    ]
}